Guide to the Mark Hall Amitin/ World of Culture for the Performing Arts, Inc. Archive MSS.121
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VII: Photographs and slides
  - Albee Directs Albee - photographs, slides, undated (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Albee Directs Albee front of house actors' photos - photographs, undated (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Edward Albee in Korea - slides, Nov 1978 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Seth Allen - photograph, undated (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Mark Amitin, various - photographs, undated (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Mark Amitin, Vietnam and Smaller Pieces- photograph, 1969 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Jo Andres - photographs, undated (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Autograph in Moscow - photographs, May 1981 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Avant Garde Arts Festival, 46th Street pier, New York City - slides, 1984 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Balinese dance - slides, undated (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Eszter Balint - photographs, undated (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Stefan Balint - photographs, undated (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Baltimore International Theatre Festival - photographs, Jun 6, 1981-Jun 14, 1981 (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - George Bartenieff - photograph, undated (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Bastian - photograph, undated (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Isha Manna Beck - photographs, undated (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - Julian Beck - photographs, Aug 22, 1951-1985 (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - Julian Beck - slides, 1965, 1984 (Box 74, Folder 18)
  - Julian Beck at Amitins - slides, 1984 (Box 74, Folder 19)
  - Julian Beck, Poltergeist II- photographs, slides, 1985 (Box 74, Folder 20)
  - Beijing Opera - slides, Sep 1983 (Box 74, Folder 21)
  - Beijing People's Art Theatre, Family( Jia) - slides, May 1984 (Box 74, Folder 22)
  - Karla Palotai Berg and Peter Berg - photographs, undated (Box 74, Folder 23)
  - Keith Berger - photographs, undated (Box 74, Folder 24)
  - Keith Berger, Sharon Diskin - photographs, 4x5 negative, undated (Box 74, Folder 25)
  - Big Apple Circus - slides, undated (Box 74, Folder 26)
  - Bread and Puppet Theatre - photographs, contact sheet, 1971 (Box 74, Folder 27)
  - Lee Breuer - photograph, undated (Box 74, Folder 28)
  - Timothy Buckley - photographs, undated (Box 74, Folder 29)
  - Bukhara, Samarkand, Tashkent - slides, 1984 (Box 74, Folder 30)
  - Steve Buscemi - photographs, undated (Box 74, Folder 31)
  - Steve Buscemi & Mark Boone Jnr. - photographs, contact sheets, undated (Box 74, Folder 32)
  - Cafe Vulgaris, created and directed by Mark Amitin, Copenhagen International Theatre Festival - slides, Jul 1981 (Box 74, Folder 33)
  - David Cale - photographs, slides, contact sheets, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 34)
  - Cameri Theatre - photographs, undated (Box 74, Folder 35)
  - Joseph Chaikin - photographs, contact sheets, undated (Box 74, Folder 36)
  - Shami Chaikin - photographs, 1974 (Box 74, Folder 37)
  - Valerie Charles - photographs, undated (Box 74, Folder 38)
  - China: Galileo- slides, undated (Box 74, Folder 39)
  - China: operas, tourism - slides, Jul 1979-Sep-83 (Box 74, Folder 40)
  - China: Teahouse- slides, Jul 1979 (Box 74, Folder 41)
  - Chinese Theatre postcards, undated (Box 74, Folder 42)
  - China various I - slides, 1979-1984 (Box 74, Folder 43)
  - China various II - slides, 1983 (Box 74, Folder 44)
  - Chinese Theatre I - slides, 1979-1984 (Box 74, Folder 45)
  - Chinese Theatre II - slides, 1979-1984 (Box 74, Folder 46)
  - Chinese Theatre III - slides, 1979-1984 (Box 74, Folder 47)
  - Raphael Cohen - photographs, contact sheets, undated (Box 74, Folder 48)
  - The Company Theatre - photographs, undated (Box 74, Folder 49)
  - Wayne County - photographs, undated (Box 74, Folder 50)
  - Denmark playgrounds, restaurants - slides, Jul 1981 (Box 74, Folder 51)
  - Divine with the Cockettes - photograph, 1970 (Box 74, Folder 52)
  - Dog Day After-noon, Judith Malina, Al Pacino color still for film - photograph, 1974 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Jango Edwards (Friends Roadshow) - photographs, contact sheets, Sep 1976 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Electra(Chaikin, Montgomery production) - photographs, contact sheets, undated (Box 75, Folder 3, Folder 5)
  - Jean Erdman - photographs, undated (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - European Festivals - photographs, contact sheets, 1975 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - European Festivals - photographs, contact sheets, 1975 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Experimental Theatre Festival, Baltimore - contact sheet, 1977 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Peter Facinelli - photograph, undated (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Richard Foreman, Pain(t), Pandering to the Masses- contact sheet, postcards, 1974 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Fourteen Karat Soul - photographs, undated (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - The Friends Roadshow (see also Jango Edwards) - photographs, contact sheets, 1975 (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Richard Ganoung - photographs, contact sheets, undated (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Jack Gelber - photograph, undated (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Gesher Theatre - photographs, undated (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Philip Glass - photographs, undated (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Michael Grando - photographs, undated (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - George Gray - slides, Feb 1986 (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - Spalding Gray - photographs, undated (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Guess Who's Coming to Dinner?- slides, Oct 1980 (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - Hauser Orkater - photographs, undated (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Wilson Heredia - photographs (one with autograph), undated (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - William Hoffmann - photograph, undated (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - Indian Puppets - slides, Jun 1980 (Box 75, Folder 23)
  - Israeli theatre - photographs, undated (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - Baba Ishangi - photographs, undated (Box 75, Folder 25)
  - Joffrey Ballet - photographs, undated (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - Jordcirkus - photographs, undated (Box 75, Folder 27)
  - Kathy Kinney - contact sheet, 35mm negs, 9x11 neg, undated (Box 75, Folder 28)
  - The Kipper Kids - photographs, contact sheets, 35mm negs, 2.5x2.5 negs, 1988 (Box 75, Folder 29)
  - Korean fan dance, masks - slides, Jul 1979 (Box 75, Folder 30)
  - La Gran Scena Opera - photographs, undated (Box 75, Folder 31)
  - John & Althea Lahr - photographs, contact sheets, undated (Box 75, Folder 32)
  - Maxine Lapidus - photographs, undated (Box 75, Folder 33)
  - Franne Lee - photograph, undated (Box 75, Folder 34)
  - Leningrad musical comedy - slides, undated (Box 75, Folder 35)
  - Le Plan K - photographs, slides, May 1980 (Box 75, Folder 36)
  - Le Plan K, Penny Arcade Peepshow- photographs, undated (Box 75, Folder 37)
  - Lindsay Kemp & Flowers Co., Salome- contact sheets, slide, Jan 1975 (Box 75, Folder 38)
  - Living Poem Theatre - photographs, undated (Box 75, Folder 39)
  - The Living Theatre - photographs, undated (Box 75, Folder 40)
  - The Living Theatre, Antigone rehearsal, Paris - photographs, slides, Jun 1982 (Box 75, Folder 41)
  - The Living Theatre, The Archeology of Sleep, France - photographs, May 1983 (Box 75, Folder 42)
  - The Living Theatre, The Archeology of Sleep, Yellow Methuselah, The One and the Many- slides, Jan 1984 (Box 75, Folder 43)
  - The Living Theatre, Julian Beck, Judith Malina, Mark Amitin, Ilion Troya - contact sheet, slides, Oct 1984 (Box 75, Folder 44)
  - The Living Theatre, The Body of God- photographs, undated (Box 75, Folder 45)
  - The Living Theatre in Brasil - photographs, contact sheets, 1971 (Box 75, Folder 46)
  - The Living Theatre in Brasil: Saramenha School, Rio Clara - photographs, Jan (?),, May 1971 (Box 75, Folder 47)
  - The Living Theatre, The Brig- 2.5x2.5 negs, undated (Box 75, Folder 48)
  - The Living Theatre, The Brig- 2.5x2.5 negs, undated (Box 75, Folder 49)
  - The Living Theatre, Capital Changes- photographs, 1998 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - The Living Theatre, Chile demonstration - contact sheets, 35 mm negs, 1973 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - The Living Theatre, Decoding Utopia(photos to be included in book) - photographs, 1951- (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - The Living Theatre fortieth anniversary celebration - photographs, undated (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - The Living Theatre, I and I- photographs, undated (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - The Living Theatre with Indians [?] - contact sheets, 35mm negs, undated (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - The Living Theatre - The Life of the Theatre - color contact sheets, 1981 (Box 78, Folder 45)
  - The Living Theatre, Love play rehearsal, Vienna - slides, Jun 1982 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - The Living Theatre madhouse play, Creteil, France - slides, 1982 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - The Living Theatre, The Maids(Genet) - photographs, undated (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - The Living Theatre, Man is Man- 4x5 negs, 2.5x2.5 negs, undated (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - The Living Theatre, Masse Mensch, Cuando, NYC - slides, 1984 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - The Living Theatre, Masse Mensch, Paris - slides, 1982 (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - The Living Theatre, The Money Tower- photographs, 1975 (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - The Living Theatre, Mysteries & Smaller Pieces- photographs, 35mm negs, undated (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - The Living Theatre, Paradise Now- photograph, 1968 (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - The Living Theatre, Poland 1931- photographs, undated (Box 76, Folder 16)
  - The Living Theatre, Prometheus, Winter Palace - photographs, slide, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 17)
  - The Living Theatre Retrospectacle - contact sheets, 1986 (Box 76, Folder 18)
  - The Living Theatre, Rules of Civility- photographs, undated (Box 76, Folder 19)
  - The Living Theatre in St Felix Str, Brooklyn - contact sheets, Jul 20, 1973 (Box 76, Folder 20)
  - The Living Theatre Strike Support Oratorium rehearsals at St Felix Street, Brooklyn - contact sheets, 35mm negs, 1973 (Box 76, Folder 21)
  - The Living Theatre, Seven Meditations on Political Sado-Masochism- photograph, undated (Box 76, Folder 22)
  - The Living Theatre, Seven Meditations on Political Sado-Masochism, Hunter college - contact sheets, 35mm negs, May 1973 (Box 76, Folder 23)
  - The Living Theatre, Seven Meditations on Political Sado-Masochism, Boston - photographs, Mar 1974 (Box 76, Folder 24)
  - The Living Theatre, Seven Meditations on Political Sado-Masochism- photographs, contact sheets, 35mm negs, undated (Box 76, Folder 25)
  - The Living Theatre, Six Public Acts, Ann Arbor, MI - slides, 1975 (Box 76, Folder 26)
  - The Living Theatre, Six Public Acts- photograph, undated (Box 76, Folder 27)
  - The Living Theatre, Tablets- photographs, contact sheets, undated (Box 76, Folder 28)
  - The Living Theatre, Theatre Now- contact Sheet, undated (Box 76, Folder 29)
  - The Living Theatre, Us- photographs, contact sheets, undated (Box 76, Folder 30)
  - The Living Theatre various - photographs, 1971 (Box 76, Folder 31)
  - The Living Theatre, Vienna - slides, Jun 1982 (Box 76, Folder 32)
  - The Living Theatre, VKTMS- contact sheets, undated (Box 76, Folder 33)
  - The Living Theatre, The Yellow Methuselah, Anne Masse premier - slides, May 1982 (Box 76, Folder 34)
  - The Living Theatre, The Yellow Methuselah, Rome - photographs, 4x5 negs, 1982 (Box 76, Folder 35)
  - The Living Theatre, The Yellow Methuselah, Rome rehearsal - slides, 1982 (Box 76, Folder 36)
  - The Living Theatre, The Yellow Methuselah, Vienna - slides, Jun 1982 (Box 76, Folder 37)
  - The Living Theatre, The Yellow Methuselah, Joyce Theatre, New York -, Jan 1984 (Box 76, Folder 38)
  - The Living Theatre, The Zero Method- photographs, undated (Box 76, Folder 39)
  - Los Angeles Mask Theatre - photographs, 1976 (Box 76, Folder 40)
  - Charles Ludlam, Bread and Puppet Theatre, Andre Gregory, Isha Manna Beck - contact, undated (Box 76, Folder 41)
  - Karen Ludwig - photographs, undated (Box 76, Folder 42)
  - Lypsinka - photograph, undated (Box 76, Folder 43)
  - Mabou Mines - photographs, 1979 (Box 76, Folder 44)
  - Juditha Malina - photographs, polaroids, 1952- (Box 76, Folder 45)
  - Judith Malina, Julian Beck - photographs, 1971- (Box 76, Folder 46)
  - The Manhattan Project- photographs, contact sheets, 1974 (Box 76, Folder 47)
  - Man is Man, NY Production with Joseph Chairin - b&w photographs, undated (Box 78, Folder 46)
  - Wayne Maugans - photographs, undated (Box 76, Folder 48)
  - Kres Mersky - photographs, undated (Box 76, Folder 49)
  - Mimi Garrard Dance Company - photographs, undated (Box 76, Folder 50)
  - Miscellaneous photographs (non-WOC clients), undated (Box 76, Folder 51)
  - Miscellaneous slides, 1981 (Box 76, Folder 52)
  - Mondo Beyondo- photograph, undated (Box 76, Folder 53)
  - Murray Louis Dance Company - photographs, undated (Box 76, Folder 54)
  - Mystery Train- photographs, 1989 (Box 76, Folder 55)
  - Roy Nathanson and the Jazz Passengers - photographs, contact sheets, undated (Box 76, Folder 56)
  - The New Cell Theatre - photographs, undated (Box 76, Folder 57)
  - Nightfire- photographs, undated (Box 76, Folder 58)
  - Mark Nizer - photographs, undated (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - The Open Theatre - photographs, 1967-1973 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Serge Ouaknine - photographs, 1977 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Palestinian National Theatre: unidentified actor, Mark Amitin, Jamal Gosheh -, 1995 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Paradise Now- 8x10 neg, 1969 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Rob Parker - photographs, undated (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Pasadena Playhouse - photographs (reprints), 1940s (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Peking Youth Art Theatre, Galileo, Peking People's Art Theatre, Teahouse-, 1979 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - The People Show - photographs, undated (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - The Performance Group (Richard Schechner, Joan MacIntosh, Steven Borst) -, undated (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - The Performance Group, Commune- photographs, 1971 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - The Performance Group, Mother Courage- photographs, slide, undated (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - The Performance Group, The Tooth of Crime- photographs, undated (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - The Permanent "I" - 35mm negs, Jul 11, 1976 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Philippe Petit - photographs, slides, 8x10 neg, undated (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - Pilobolus - photographs, undated (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - Poetry reading, Paris, Village Voice Bookstore - slides, 1982 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Polish Mime Ballet Theatre - contact sheets (photocopies), 1976 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - Provisional Theatre - contact sheets, 1976 (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - David Quane (with Mark Amitin) - photograph, undated (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - Rosemary Quinn - photographs, undated (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - Reality Theatre - photographs, undated (Box 77, Folder 22)
  - Hanon Reznikov - photographs, undated (Box 77, Folder 23)
  - The Ridiculous Theatrical Company (see also Charles Ludlam) - photographs, 1974 (Box 77, Folder 24)
  - Luca Ronconi, John Lion - photographs, undated (Box 77, Folder 25)
  - Russian Theatre - photographs, undated (Box 77, Folder 26)
  - Leeny Sack - photograph, undated (Box 77, Folder 27)
  - San Francisco Mime Troupe - photographs, slides, contact sheets, 1974, 1980 (Box 77, Folder 28)
  - San Francisco Mime Troupe, Tabakov- slides, 1981 (Box 77, Folder 29)
  - Shaliko Company - photographs, undated (Box 77, Folder 30)
  - Shanghai People's Art Theatre, Shanghai Performing Arts Troupe - slides, Sep 1983 (Box 77, Folder 31)
  - Shanghai Youth Art Theatre, Anthony and Cleopatra- slides, May 5, 1984 (Box 77, Folder 32)
  - Sam Shepard, Magic Theatre, San Francisco, CA - contact sheet, May 1976 (Box 77, Folder 33)
  - Stewart Sherman - photographs, 1979 (Box 77, Folder 34)
  - Evanly Shin/ Evan Schindler - contact sheet, undated (Box 77, Folder 35)
  - James Siena - photograph, undated (Box 77, Folder 36)
  - Agnes Smedley film locations, Shanghai - slides, Aug 1985 (Box 77, Folder 37)
  - Solaris - photographs, 1979 (Box 77, Folder 38)
  - Squat Theatre - photographs, undated (Box 77, Folder 39)
  - Shirley Stoler - photographs, undated (Box 77, Folder 40)
  - Studio Theatre in Warsaw - photographs, undated (Box 77, Folder 41)
  - Cecil Taylor - photographs, undated (Box 77, Folder 42)
  - Teatro Officina in Lisbon - photographs, Jun 1975 (Box 77, Folder 43)
  - Theatre de Soleil, L'Age d'Or- photographs, contact sheets, May 1975 (Box 77, Folder 44)
  - Theatre Laboratoire Vicinal - photographs, 1975-1977 (Box 77, Folder 45)
  - Theatre various - slides, 1964-1982 (Box 77, Folder 46)
  - Theatre Workshop in Boston - photographs, Apr 1975 (Box 77, Folder 47)
  - Tokyo, Korea, Manila, Macao - slides, 1984 (Box 77, Folder 48)
  - Toronto Dance Theatre - photographs, undated (Box 77, Folder 49)
  - Travel various (China, Yugoslavia, Italy) - slides, 1979 (Box 77, Folder 50)
  - Trocadero Gloxinia Ballet Company - photographs, 1974 (Box 77, Folder 51)
  - Ilion Troya - photograph, undated (Box 77, Folder 52)
  - Unidentified - contact sheets, 35mm negs, undated (Box 77, Folder 53)
  - Untitled b&w photograph, undated (Box 78, Folder 47)
  - USSR - slides, 35mm negs, 1981 (Box 77, Folder 54)
  - Jean-Claude van Itallie - photographs, undated (Box 77, Folder 55)
  - Jean-Claude van Itallie, The Balcony- photographs, undated (Box 77, Folder 56)
  - Jean-Claude van Itallie, A Fable- photograph, Jan 1975 (Box 77, Folder 57)
  - Jean-Claude van Itallie, King of the United States- photographs, undated (Box 77, Folder 58)
  - Various slides, 1963-1984 (Box 77, Folder 59)
  - Ron Vawter - photograph, undated (Box 77, Folder 60)
  - Susan Ventura/ Penny Arcade - photograph, undated (Box 77, Folder 61)
  - Westbeth Playwrights' Feminist Collective - photograph, undated (Box 77, Folder 62)
  - The Wiz - photographs, undated (Box 77, Folder 63)
  - World of Culture clients - photographs, slides, undated (Box 77, Folder 64)
  - World of Culture Tours - photographs, undated (Box 77, Folder 65)
  - Cao Yu, Columbia University lecture - photographs, contact sheets, Mar 27, 1980 (Box 77, Folder 66)
  - Paul Zaloom - photographs, contact sheets, undated (Box 77, Folder 67)
- Series VIII: Posters
  In addition to posters there are some oversize photographs (The Living Theatre) as well as sketches and technical drawings in this series. There is also a large scrapbook in folder 1 of box 78. Materials are arranged alphabetically according to theatre group or director. A performance title is given only when no theatre group or director is indicated. The two boxes (one small, one large) are alphabetized independently.
  - Albee Directs Albee Production Calendars, 1978-1979 (Box 78, Folder 1a)
    A handmade calendar with rehearsal, touring, and financial annotations.
  - Mark Amitin scrapbook, undated (Box 78, Folder 1b)
  - Academie Experimentale des Theatres, 1996 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Ann Arbor 8mm Film and Video Festival, undated (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Bread and Puppet Theatre, undated (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Tim Buckley and the Twisters, undated (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - David Cale, 1987 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Cameri Theatre, 1993 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Central Park Summer Stage, 1986 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Danspace Project, undated (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Downtown(newsletter of Lower Manhattan Cultural Council), May 1983 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - En Garde Arts presents Another Person is a Foreign Country, undated (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Jean Erdman, undated (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Festival Mondial du Theatre de Nancy, undated (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - Israel Museum Jerusalem, undated (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - Jordcirkus/ Chris Torch, 1986 (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - The Kitchen, 1982-1983 (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - La Gran Scena Opera Co., Feb 1986 (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - Latin American Fair of Opinion, undated (Box 78, Folder 18)
  - The Living Theatre, various, 1991 (Box 78, Folder 19)
  - Wayne Maugans and Marcy Drogin, Heat, undated (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - Nightfire Co., 1983 (Box 78, Folder 21)
  - Deirdre O'Connell, undated (Box 78, Folder 22)
  - Serge Ouaknine, Une Nuit a Shanghai, 1984 (Box 78, Folder 23)
  - The People Show, undated (Box 78, Folder 24)
  - The Performance Group, undated (Box 78, Folder 25)
  - Leeny Sack, The Survivor and the Translator, undated (Box 78, Folder 26)
  - The San Francisco Mime Troupe, various, undated (Box 78, Folder 27)
  - Steven Sater, Alvrone, Nov 1985 (Box 78, Folder 28)
  - The Shaliko Company, undated (Box 78, Folder 29)
  - Robert Sherman, 1980 (Box 78, Folder 30)
  - Sleaze Festival opens at 8th Str, undated (Box 78, Folder 31)
  - Soon 3, 1975 (Box 78, Folder 32)
  - Steve Speck and the Dots, 1983 (Box 78, Folder 33)
  - Stockholms Internationella Teaterfestival, 1985 (Box 78, Folder 34)
  - Studio II, undated (Box 78, Folder 35)
  - Theatre Now at the BAM, undated (Box 78, Folder 36)
  - Theatre of the Eighth Decade, Nov 8, 1972 (Box 78, Folder 37)
  - Thespian Festival, 1983 (Box 78, Folder 38)
  - Roger Tolle and Dancers, Nov 1986 (Box 78, Folder 39)
  - Toronto Dance Theatre, undated (Box 78, Folder 40)
  - Ubu, number 4, Mar 1971 (Box 78, Folder 41)
  - Unconventional Constitutional Convention, Sep 29, 1986 (Box 78, Folder 42)
  - Paul Zaloom, undated (Box 78, Folder 43)
  - Zone Collaborations, 1981 (Box 78, Folder 44)
  - Albee Directs Albee - posters, banner, ground plan, rubber stamp, 1978-1979 (Folder 1 Left, Box 81, Box 82, Folder 1)
  - BACA Downtown - The Fringe Series, 1988 (Folder 7 Left)
  - The Balcony, 1990 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Keith Berger, Sharon Diskin, Undated (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Steve Buscemi and Mark Boone Jnr., undated (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - David Cale, various, 1987 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Joseph Chaikin, Undated (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Lucinda Childs and Robert Wilson, undated (Folder 10)
  - Columbia College Chicago, undated (Folder 6 Left)
  - Danspace Project, Undated (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Earthcircus, Undated (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - Festival Mondial du Theatre, 1973 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Glenn Lund Dance Company, 1983 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - The Kipper Kids, Feb 1988 (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - La Mama Repertory Company, 1975 (Folder 10 Left)
  - Le Plan K, undated (Folder 4 Left)
  - The Living Theatre, various, 1972 (Folder 5 Left)
  - Matthew Maguire, Propaganda, Undated (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Moerder, Hoffnung der Frauen: Ein Explodistisches Schauspiel nach Oskar Kokoscha, undated (Folder 8 Left)
  - New York Now, 1987 October 21-October 24 (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Tom O'Horgan and Victor Lipari, Undated (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - The Performance Group, Undated (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Solaris Dance Theatre, Undated (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Studio 2, undated (Folder 9 Left)
  - Theatre Laboratoire Vicinal Belgium, Undated (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - Boris Tissot, 1980 (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - Jean-Claude van Itallie, Undated (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - Wroclaw Confrontations of the Open Theatre, undated (Folder 3 Left)
- Series IX: Printed matter
  These materials are arranged alphabetically but not in folders.
  - American Film, Nov 1990 (Box 80, Folder data_value_missing_6a28def1beed7e72b472fca2680a7f81)
  - American Theatre, Jul 1984Aug 1984 (Box 80, Folder data_value_missing_69b06922d06f6cc888fcb6b9437128ae)
  - American Theatre, Nov 1996 (Box 80, Folder data_value_missing_b86dc466bb345ee343a29869a5e634d8)
  - Anthology Film Archives, Jan 1992-Feb 1992 (Box 80, Folder data_value_missing_b48885d490e311fc37330b489a333683)
  - Arts Magazine, Nov 1986 (Box 80, Folder data_value_missing_3ecfca60879e58f8f9be6a15f9dc9afe)
  - Black Book, Fall 1996 (Box 80, Folder data_value_missing_b55adbd0fbb68a68ceadadc91da05661)
  - Black Book, Spring 1997 (Box 80, Folder data_value_missing_4eb98fe00078190aeac76fc27e6648e2)
  - Black Book, Summer 1997 (Box 80, Folder data_value_missing_82a406e9598297755067fc2aeb4f311f)
  - Chelsea Clinton News, Jul 1993Sep 1993 (Box 80, Folder data_value_missing_cc9ea4a91197563a9330ea8d6fe131a0)
  - Cover Arts New York, Apr 1987 (Box 80, Folder data_value_missing_44366950d1fb970f5d5b450b8ba7c3a2)
  - The Dispossessed Al Mashbeen, undated (Box 80)
  - Downtown, May 20, 1987 (Box 80, Folder data_value_missing_401a5adb883db21218bbfd8080256bf2)
  - Entertainment Weekly, Nov 15, 1991 (Box 80, Folder data_value_missing_7bc1a9aca15566280e2e01d59e7d018d)